Sir Kin'emon! Sir Denjiro!
Best of luck!
To you as well!
We have no money, Lord Oden!
Truly?!
We have nothing to eat for supper!
Okay, I have a job for you!
Go to town and beg for food!
Again?!
I am sure it was painful, everyone.
Kin...
For now, let us march on.
Izo...
Have you made peace with perishing here?
I will not miss another chance to die.
Then let us go.
Okiku.
Make your choice, samurai of Orochi!
Do you wanna die alongside
your lord Orochi here?!
Or will you conquer the world with us?!
I'm well aware of how loyal you samurai are.
I admire even those of you who challenge us!
The 5,000 strong Oniwabanshu,
the ninja force of Wano!
Allow us to serve you!
Likewise, the samurai of Wano, 5,000 strong!
Henceforth, we serve you!
Welcome aboard!
Shogun Orochi...
Well, that's that...
Good to hear! I didn't wanna turn coat
and have to kill you guys outta nowhere!
Pleasure workin' with ya!
They have no right to be called samurai!
Hold it in for now, Boss Hyogoro!
To think you actually brought
that worthless shogun's troops to our side...
You're not half bad.
Now our forces are really coming together.
Let me go!
No! Get off me!
Keep them restrained.
I'm not letting you get away with this!
If Shinobu can escape,
we still have a chance!
I'm sorry, Onami!
I must advance!
Hurry and help Momo!
Lord Oden knew!
He knew that felling Orochi
would change nothing!
The only one in need of defeat for
the past twenty years has been Kaido!
As it stands now, within Wano...
there's no shogun or
any samurai serving him!
The unwitting citizens of the Flower Capital...
must be enjoying the festivities too much
to see that this will be their last day.
Hey, brat!
I've had my doubts for a while.
A coward like you...
can't be the son of
a daredevil like Kozuki Oden!
I...
This execution will bring about
an end to the old Wano.
Looking back on that day twenty years ago...
inside that burning castle...
you never answered my question!
Please... save me...!
What is your name?
Answer!
Father!
Somebody, help me!
If you aren't the son
of Kozuki Oden and Toki,
I'll call off the execution immediately.
After all, such a false accusation
would tarnish my reputation.
However, if you still insist
on calling yourself their son...
you'll face the same fate Oden did.
I'll ask you one more time, brat.
What is your name?!
Viceroy Kaido is so generous!
All the rugrat has to do is lie
and he gets to live!
Think up a good name, kiddo!
Even if you have to lie,
please choose to survive!
Lord Momonosuke!
What?! Then that boy...
is the real Kozuki Momonosuke?!
That's right!
Oden's retainers are all alive!
What?!
Intruders!
Outta my way!
If all the Red Scabbards samurai
I saw that day are...
If they're all alive, then that's wonderful!
Just wonderful!
I can hardly believe it!
Momonosuke is waiting for you!
Let's hurry!
The Nine Red Scabbards are here, right?!
Lemme go, Yamabro!
Yamabro? Why are you calling me that?
Please stop, Young Master Yamato!
Stop!
Young Master Yamato and Straw Hat Luffy
are heading your way!
To the Performance Floor?
Yes! We'll catch them!
Don't bother.
You're no match–
They dare to mess with my men?!
Yamato!
You're gonna pay for this!
No way! Usopp, not over here!
It looks dangerous!
You heard the broadcast earlier!
They're gonna kill Momo!
The giants!
They'll gobble us up!
Turn around, Usopp!
Stow your fears, Chopper!
We fought an Emperor to a standstill!
Believe in the General Franky! It was
tough enough to withstand Big Mom's attacks!
I can't!
I can't handle these monsters!
Never give up!
Never surrender!
Tank Commander Chopper,
what are your orders?!
Retreat! Retreat!
Are you scared?!
Cut the "samurai" crap!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates someday!
Because your father is a great man...
and you will one day carry
this nation on your shoulders.
The meaning of your name?
Yes!
I want you to grow into a compassionate,
open-minded, and admirable man.
Momo!
Momo...
means peerless!
My name is...
Kozuki Momonosuke!
One day, I will become...
the shogun of Wano!
Lord Momonosuke!
I swear I will save you no matter
the cost, Lord Momonosuke!
Well said, Momonosuke!
We're almost there, Luffy!
Let me take these off!
I promised you!
If you would!
However, just to be safe...
please throw them far away.
Although, I doubt they'll explode...
Is Wano filled with only halfwits?!
Father... Mother...
I merely wished to be a man...
who would be free of shame when
next he sees you in the afterlife.
Hiyori, I wish I could see you again,
even if for a moment...
I do not want to die!
I do not want to cry!
A samurai should not cry in front of others...
How shameful...
They came off!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Wh–
Luffy?!
Dammit!
That freaking cowrilla!
He was going to kill me!
What was that explosion?!
Go find out, pronto!
Now it's clear to me.
That man is no longer my father!
Was this your doing, you spoiled brat?!
Hold on, Yamabro!
You stupid old man!
We made it just in time...
but it's not gonna be me or Yamabro.
We're not the ones who'll start this battle!
The Red Scabbards!
Where did they come from?!
The rulers of the minks?!
They're alive!
You damn ghosts!
Prepare for my counterattack!
Izo!
Hey, dumbasses!
Quit drinking already!
Go grab your weapons!
It's a raid!
Are you...
Kyoshiro?!
Kaido!
You half-ghost bastards!
Surrender Name And Thoughts...
Calm all Hesitation!
Your blades...
cannot cut me!
Stake your lives on this blow!
Oden!
Never set foot in Wano again!
SNATCH!
Oden Two-Sword Style:
Halcyon Totsuka!
The scar Oden left me with...
Why does it hurt?
How do these blades pierce my body?!
Do not underestimate my samurai!
They can forget me...
for all I care...
but...
my spirit will live on!
Are they using Oden's ryuo?!
Pierce through!
They really are Oden's retainers!
They sure are strong!
Quite the deadly banquet!
Did Kaido kick the bucket?
Fight back!
Kill those Red Scabbard rats!
So Straw Hat, Kid, and all the others were
merely distractions for this ambush?!
Stay alert, you guys!
There could still be intruders around here!
Spot on!
Open your ears, weaklings!
We won't let you bring harm
to Kin'emon and his samurai!
Alright! Let's get in on this!
We'll give Kaido another beating!
There you are!
Yamato!
Headbutt!
Ulti!
The nerve, striking me as you did!
I am on your side,
yet you brutally assaulted me,
and now you're running around
the place with that Straw Hat...
Whatever are you doing?!
Nothing to get upset over.
The day that I become
Kozuki Oden is finally here!
What are you talking about?! Are you crazy?!
Young Master Yamato, we have a problem!
Your father was just attacked,
and now the floor is swarming with enemies!
Please stop fooling around!
I'm well aware!
I'm not your ally anymore,
and I don't give a damn if my father dies!
– What?!
What is it this time?
This banquet is getting far too rowdy...
Gum-Gum...
Elephant Gun!
That boy...
Oh crap!
She saw Luffy!
Big Mom!
But I'm busy right now!
I finally found you...
Straw Hat!
Ulti...
Mortar!
Carrot! Let's make a break for it!
Got it!
Better get ready!
Black Ball!
Hey, are you okay?!
Here goes!
Same here!
Thundercloud Rod!
Eleclaw!
Ninpo: Ectoplasm Thunder!
We did it!
You came into my territory
and disgraced my crew!
So I came all the way from
Totto Land to kill you!
Straw Hat!
Why are you here?
And don't tell me it's to take down Kaido,
because that'd be too damn rich.
It's not that!
What?
Luffy?!
What do you mean, Sir Straw Hat?!
It's not, Luffy?!
No!
I'm...
After twenty years,
the Red Scabbards samurai
will come to get their revenge...
Nobody believed Orochi's delusions,
but it would seem they're coming to pass.
I can't believe you made
common cause with pirates.
The rumor about the shadows
at the ruins of Oden Castle...
Punk Hazard.
Dressrosa.
The phantom island Zou.
And the crew behind it all,
the Straw Hat Pirates!
By some curious coincidence,
you people were hiding in the shadows
of my enemies, the Straw Hats.
Some of you held out for twenty years,
while others jumped ahead and ran about,
and just like that, your troops were gathered.
But pirates will stab you in the back!
The moment they sense defeat,
they'll abandon you and run.
I've already taken Straw Hat Luffy out once!
You slander the man!
Sir Luffy and your band
could not be more different!
You, Kaido, the officers, Orochi,
and every last person under them!
I'm here to kick all your asses!
He is the man who will stand
at the pinnacle of the sea someday!
Even if we die, he shall live on!
Wano will see daybreak once more!
Because...
such was the promise we made to our lord!
It's gonna be an all-out war!
Don't push your luck.
You only have a few hundred troops!
She's right, numbskulls.
What?
It's an emergency!
Thousands of intruders
are entering from the rear!
What?!
How's that possible?!
Let's go!
Fine!
If you want it so bad...
I'll cut you up as much as you like.
Screw you!
Exactly...
Right back at you!
But why...?!
A samurai...
Sir Zorojuro! We are by your side!
This is Point C!
It's all the samurai we caught
in the Flower Capital...
and the prisoners from Udon!
What the hell is happening?!
Punk...
Gibson!
Don't fall behind, boys!
Thank you for clearing the way for us this far.
Keep your thanks.
I'm only here to take Kaido's head.
Get in my way, and I'll take yours too.
Appreciate the warning.
Room!
Go to hell!
Amputate!
Shambles!
What?
The pirates that Sir Kin'emon brought...
are pretty damn strong!
How did this all happen?!
A former Warlord, Law, has arrived as well.
They're all working together and gaining power!
Say what?!
Your Awesomeness!
There's more?!
At the entrance of the island,
Marco the Phoenix
and Perospero are working together–
Hey! What happened?!
Hello?!
Candy Maiden!
What's going on?!
Why are they teaming up?!
And now begins the ogre extermination.
I'll turn every last lickety-one of
the Beast Pirates into candy men.
Attention, drunkards of Onigashima!
Tonight's banquet is canceled!
Go grab your weapons!
It's an enemy raid!
Everyone...
Kaido may be gone, but there are
still three Superstars present.
I'm sure there will be a chance!
Lord Momonosuke!
Please wait just a little longer...
Let's do this!
We will take back Wano!
I heard that, Straw Hat!
You say you'll kick my ass?
Then go ahead and try!
I accept your challenge!
I'll show you the world's greatest army!
Sir Luffy!
Many thanks!
Kin'emon! I'll catch up later!
Kaido...
I've completely sobered up.
If it's a fight to the death you want,
it's best out in the open.
Just like that day...
But unlike that day, Oden's already dead.
There's one more difference from that day.
We deduced that when you turn into a dragon,
you wouldn't be able to fight in the dome.
You can't understand
how I've longed for this day!
You will know our rage
when we beat it into you!
The minks...
We brought the warriors from our kingdom.
A flurry of snow in the clear sky...
Perfect for watching the full moon.